Previously on Reacher...
《烈探雷徹》前情提要
He said 650 at 100K each.
他說:“六千五 每手十萬”
It could be a transfer of 65 million, a $65 million cover-up,
可能是六千五百萬的轉賬 六千五百萬的掩飾費
a $65 million bribe.
六千五百萬的賄賂款
We got a suspect.
我們找到了一個嫌疑人
Azhari Mahmoud.
阿扎里馬哈茂德
He's known to Interpol as a weapons broker for terrorist organizations.
國際刑警組織 知道他是恐怖組織的武器經紀人
He's a ghost. No pictures of him anywhere.
“他如幽靈一般 任何地方都沒有他的照片”
If these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
如果這些是分數 那寫下這些數字的人就太粗心了
On each sheet there's 26 or 27 numerical tabulations.
每張紙上有26或27個數字列表
So, the real question is what kind of somethings were they counting?
真正的問題是 他們在算什么事的時間
You don't have to be lonely tonight.
今晚你不必孤單
There were hit men who tried to kill us in Atlantic City.
在大西洋城的時候 有殺手曾經想殺了我們
They failed, but they had a parking pass for a company called New Age.
他們失敗了 但他們有一張 叫新時代的公司的停車證
New Age is an aerospace company.
新時代是一家航空航天公司
I'm Marlo Burns, New Age Director of Operations.
我是馬洛伯恩斯 新時代的運營總監
The parking pass was issued to a man named Trevor Saropian.
停車證被發給了 一個叫特雷弗薩羅皮安的男人
- Where's his car? - We decided to take it with us.
- 他的車在哪兒  - 我們決定把車帶走
Holy shit. It's Swan.
天啊 是斯旺
He was working at New Age
他曾在新世紀工作
with the people who've been trying to kill us.
跟一直想殺了我們的這群人一起
Great. Well, we drove a car through a window
真棒 我們開車撞破窗戶
so that I could read workers comp pleadings
這樣我就可以閱讀 一位五年前在新時代
for a secretary who slipped on New Age stairs five years ago.
滑倒的秘書的工傷賠償訴狀了
So glad we risked prison for that.
真開心我們為此冒著坐牢的風險
Yeah, I got nothing, too. No new information.
是啊 我也一無所獲 沒有新線索
Well, I wouldn't say we haven't found any new information.
我倒是覺得我們發現了一些新線索
I mean, we've got three special investigators dead,
我們有三名特別調查員死亡
one in the wind,
一名在逃
and the one who's missing just happens to be the one who worked for New Age.
而失蹤的那位剛好在新時代工作過
What? Look, someone's got to say it.
怎么了 總得有人說出來
Was Swan working with these guys or with these guys?
斯旺是這些人的同事還是同謀
Swan's not dirty.
斯旺是良民
- Look, man, we all want to believe that he isn't... - I know Swan. We all do.
- 我們都想相信他沒... - 我了解斯旺 我們都了解
And you don't think there's even a chance...
你覺得那一點可能性都沒有嗎
No. I don't.
絕不可能
Focus on what we found.
專注于我們的發現
Brad?
“布拉德”
Stacy?
史黛西
This is a brad.
我說的是這種“布拉德”
That is a fastener. Two names for something that size is stupid.
那是緊固件 這么小的東西 居然有兩個名字 太蠢了
So is this conversation.
這段對話也很蠢
Well, speaking of names,
說起名字
just found our man in the employee directory.
我剛在員工目錄中 發現了我們的人的名字
Seems Swan's title was assistant director of security.
看來斯旺的職位是安全總監助理
Shane Langston, director of security.
“謝恩蘭斯頓 安全總監”
Maybe he's the guy I got on the phone in Atlantic City.
也許在大西洋城 跟我通話的就是這個人
Why would you say that?
何出此言
He's the security boss and bosses give orders
他是安全部門的老大 負責發號施令
and the guys we killed had orders to take us out.
我們殺掉的那些人 接到命令要干掉我們
Just a theory. He could be the guy that got Swan caught up in all this.
這只是推測 他可能是 讓斯旺陷入這一切的罪魁禍首
Well, if Swan didn't pull him into it first...
如果不是斯旺先讓他卷進去的話
I already told you... Aren't you the guy that said that assumptions kill?
- 我已經跟你說了... - 你不是說假設害死人嗎
Well, you're assuming that Swan's the same guy he was back in the 110.
你在假設斯旺 離開110小組后沒有變化
Hey, this is the guy Reacher chased down outside of Saropian's house.
嘿 這就是雷徹 在薩羅皮安家外面追的那個人
Same photo as his ID badge.
跟他身份證的照片一致
Associate security officer.
副安全官員
Well, that's great.
真不錯
Swan, Collins,
斯旺 柯林斯
that's two New Age security personnel somehow involved in this.
兩名新時代的安全部門人員與此有關
Now we got to look into all these fuckers. Don't forget Marlo Burns.
- 現在我們得調查所有這些混蛋 - 別忘了馬洛伯恩斯
She knew she was sending us right into a buzzsaw when she gave us Saropian's address.
是她置我們于險境 她給了我們薩羅皮安的地址
So, the entire company's suspect.
所以整個公司都很可疑
We got over a thousand employees. How we gonna tackle that?
這個公司有一千多名員工 我們怎么查這么多人
One at a time.
一次一個
Last night you asked for a late night warrant for some defense firm,
昨晚 你申請了 某國防公司的深夜搜查令
and an hour later, the place is hit with a smash-and-grab.
而一個小時后 這地方就發生了入室盜竊
Okay, do you know how that makes this department look?
你知道這讓我們看起來像什么嗎
Like we're five steps behind everything.
就好像我們步步落后一樣
I made those applications when I had enough for a warrant.
我收集到了足夠多的證據 才申請的搜查令
And while you were waiting for them, all the evidence that you would have collected
而在你等待搜查令的時候 你本該從那里收集的證據
from that place is all cleaned out.
已經全部被帶走了
And I'll bet you that it is those tin soldiers
我跟你打賭 就是那些
that you were supposed to be keeping your black eye on.
給你打出黑眼圈的破軍人干的
It wasn't the army brats. I made it crystal clear to them
不是那群軍隊混混干的 我跟他們說得很清楚
not to color outside the lines. Oh, I see.
- 讓他們守規矩  - 我知道了
You thought, if you told them nicely, they'd play along?
你覺得你好好跟他們說話 他們就會配合
You're NYPD.
你是紐約市警察局的
These are fucking PIs, for Chrissakes.
天啊 這些人都是他媽的私家偵探
Is this too fucking much for you, Russo?
這超出你的能力范圍了嗎 拉索
Lieutenant, lower your voice.
中尉 小聲點
Lower my voice?
小聲點
You're telling me to lower my voice in my own fucking office?
你讓我在我自己的辦公室里 講話小聲點
Okay.
好吧
Would you please go and find out what they learned, all right?
請你去了解一下 他們都發現了什么 好嗎
Am I asking you nicely enough, Russo?
我這么說話夠客氣了吧 拉索
I'll get it handled. Great.
- 我會處理好的 - 很好
Close the door.
關門
Who put this song on?
誰放的這首歌
This is the Talking Heads.
這是傳聲頭像樂隊的歌
You got beef with the Talking Heads? We're in New York.
你跟傳聲頭像樂隊有仇嗎  我們現在在紐約呢
They're a New York band.
他們是紐約的樂隊
They're a Rhode Island band that moved to New York
搬到了紐約的羅德島樂隊
and no, I don't have a beef with them. It's just...
沒 我跟他們沒仇 只是
"Road to Nowhere," when we're sitting here getting nowhere,
《此路不通》  剛好我們坐在這兒毫無進展
seems a little defeatist.
貌似有點晦氣
Besides, it's not even their best song.
而且這不是他們最好的歌
Probably prefer "Psycho Killer."
我更喜歡《變態殺手》
Um, I might have something.
我可能找到線索了
I've been scrubbing the drives for everything Swan-related.
我一直在找U盤里 所有和斯旺有關的內容
- And? - And I found an anomaly.
- 然后呢  - 我發現了一件反常的事
He's the assistant director of security,
他是安全總監助理
so all of his emails have Langston-- his boss--
他所有的電子郵件 都抄送了他的上司蘭斯頓
and a half-dozen other security personnel cc'd on them.
以及其他六名安保人員
Makes sense. I mean, they're a team. They share information.
合情合理 他們是一個團隊 得共享信息
But he didn't share everything.
但他沒有分享一切
There are multiple emails between Swan and our old friend Marlo Burns.
有幾封郵件是斯旺 和我們的老朋友馬洛伯恩斯的
Just them. No one else copied.
只有他們倆 沒有抄送其他人
About what?
是關于什么的
Music, but not really.
音樂 但又不全是
How do you know?
你怎么知道
He wrote,
他寫道
"I was listening to an album the other day,
“前幾天我在聽一張專輯
thought you might like it. Jimi Hendrix, Bold as Love.
“我覺得你可能會喜歡 吉米亨德里克斯的《大膽如愛》
The sixth song is amazing. Take a listen, tell me what you think."
“第六首歌太贊了 聽聽看 告訴我你的想法”
Swan hated Hendrix. Anything with hard guitar.
斯旺很討厭亨德里克斯 他討厭任何吵鬧的吉他曲...
No Skynyrd, no Hendrix, no Zeppelin, no Who.
不彈斯金納德 齊柏林 亨德里克斯和誰人樂隊的歌
I mean, that was his rule. He's leaving everyone else off the email
- 這是他的原則 - 他沒有讓其他人看這封郵件
and saying he loved something we know he hated.
而他在郵件里說他喜歡 我們知道他討厭的東西
Could be code.
可能是暗號
Or it could be a guy trying to get laid.
或者也可能是春心萌動
I mean, I once told a girl I loved Georgia O'Keeffe.
我曾經跟一個女孩說 我喜歡喬治亞歐姬芙
We say things.
我們會說這種話
Yeah. It says the sixth track is called "Little Wing."
是的 我查到第六首歌叫《小翅膀》
Hold on.
等等
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley? Not nearly enough.
- 我說過你很聰明嗎 內格利  - 還遠遠不夠
Right here. A file on a federal defense project called Little Wing,
這里 這是一份聯邦國防項目的文件 項目名叫“小翅膀”
by far the biggest contract New Age has ever had.
這是迄今為止 新時代簽下的最大的合同
Four times the size of anything I've seen anywhere else in their records.
是我在其他記錄中見過的四倍
A nine-figure contract.
一份九位數的合同
People have murdered for less.
人們為了更少的利益殺人
Look at this interoffice memo.
看看這份辦公室內部備忘錄
Seems a test for the Little Wing tech was held for some military brass,
他們似乎為一些軍事要員 甚至包括一位參議員
even a senator.
對小翅膀科技進行了測試
But what kind of test? And where?
什么測試 在哪兒測的
Doesn't say,
上面沒寫
but they do note that Senator Malcolm Lavoy
但他們確實指出 參議員馬爾科姆拉沃伊
assured he would do all he could to get the congressional votes to make Little Wing a reality.
保證他會獲得國會的選票 讓小翅膀變成現實
And I quote,
我引用原文
"He fully believes in the work we're doing here at New Age
“他完全相信我們 在新時代做的這項工作
and will do whatever it takes to help us."
“并且會不惜一切代價幫助我們”
Lavoy would fully believe in Snuffleupagus you pay him enough.
如果你給的錢夠多 拉沃伊連《芝麻街》的史納菲都信
You know this guy?
你知道這個人
By reputation. In D.C., Lavoy's what's known as a paper bag.
有所耳聞 在華盛頓特區 拉沃伊被稱為“紙袋”
His politics and his vote go whichever way the wind's blowing.
他的政治方針和投票都飄忽不定
He's known to do some shady shit.
眾所周知 他會做見不得人的事
So, if New Age stands to make a fortune on
所以如果新時代能靠政府合同發財
a government contract and Lavoy is his champion in Congress,
而拉沃伊是他們在國會的擁護者
it stands to reason New Age is the wind blowing Lavoy's bag.
這就說明新時代 讓拉沃伊的口袋裝得滿滿的
That sounds wrong.
這聽起來不對
So, Swan, who's missing, maybe dirty, maybe not,
所以 失蹤且尚不清楚 是否是良民的斯旺
is code-texting Marlo Burns, who tried to have us killed
給之前想殺了我們的馬洛伯恩斯
about a program supported
發了含有代碼的郵件
by an ethically-compromised politician.
其內容是關于 一個道德敗壞的政客支持的項目
We need talk to Malcolm Lavoy.
我們得跟馬爾科姆拉沃伊談談
We'll never get close enough to a senator to find out what he may or may not know.
我們永遠沒法接近參議員 從他口中套話
Oh, we don't need to. Those guys never even know what they're voting for.
我們不需要接近他 這些人 從來都不清楚自己在給什么投票
Thousand-page bills, the legislative record, they don't read that stuff.
一千頁的法案 立法記錄 他們不會讀那些東西的
They just vote the way they're told to. But his legislative director--
他們只會按照被告知的方式投票 但他的立法主任
they're the guys who actually craft and draft the laws,
實際上是他們制定并起草法案
which is good for us because those guys have no security detail.
這對我們有利 因為這些人沒有安保人員
Okay, but why would those people talk to us?
這些人為什么要跟我們說呢
I can make it so they'll be begging to tell us what they know.
我可以讓他們說話 讓他們求著告訴我們他們知道的事
Something you want to share with the class?
你有什么想跟我們分享的事情嗎
Look, there's a lot of powerful people in D.C. with, uh...
聽著 華盛頓特區有很多有權勢的人
confidential problems.
都有見不得光的事
Mainly unsavory, but legal, things they do
主要是不大光彩 但是合法的
in private that they'd rather not get made public.
是一些他們不愿公開的私人行為
My job is to make sure that their personal business stays personal.
我的工作就是 確保他們的私事永不見光
And the people who know secrets, they keep those secrets.
而知道秘密的人會保守住這些秘密
So, you blackmail?
所以 你敲詐勒索
I incentivize.
我是激勵他們
Sounds sleazy, O'D.
聽起來很不道德 奧唐納
It's sleazy-adjacent.
比不道德差那么一點
Hey, I got private school tuition to pay for, okay?
嘿 我得付私立學校的學費 好嗎
I never break the law.
我從不違法
I simply present the facts to people and let them know
我只是把事實擺在人們面前 讓他們知道
which way the river's gonna flow if they choose the wrong course of action.
如果他們做錯了選擇會發生什么
You give me ten minutes to make some phone calls,
給我十分鐘打幾個電話
I'll get the name of the legislative director and an Achilles' heel.
我會找到立法主任的名字 和他的致命弱點
Do it.
動手吧
All right.
好的
Thank you.
謝謝
Reacher, I know you don't want to talk about Swan...
我知道你不想說斯旺...
Swan's clean. If he wasn't, he wouldn't have disappeared like the rest of the guys.
斯旺是清白的 如果他有問題 他不會像其他人一樣消失
But he didn't disappear like the rest of the guys.
但他并沒有像其他人一樣消失
His body was never found His place wasn't trashed.
他的尸體始終沒被發現 他的家也沒被毀
He wouldn't just leave his dog to die. Not who Swan was.
他不會就這么讓他的狗渴死 斯旺不是那種人
Maybe.
也許吧
Or maybe he ran off so fast
也許他迅速逃跑
because he knew three pissed-off soldiers and a kaiju were coming for him.
因為他知道三個憤怒的士兵 和一頭怪獸會去找他
Dog was collateral damage.
狗受到了附帶傷害
Okay, look, we don't know what Swan's been up to since the 110th ended. Right?
好吧 聽我說 我們不知道 110小組解散后 斯旺在忙什么
I mean, he could have money problems. He could have been taking payoffs.
他可能缺錢 可能收臟錢
Would you believe it if somebody told you I was taking payoffs?
如果有人告訴你我收臟錢 你會相信嗎
No.
不會
I'm just saying
我只是說
maybe we don't know some people as well as we think we do.
也許我們不像 我們想象中那么了解某些人
There's no way the Tony Swan I recruited is a part of this.
我招募的托尼斯旺 絕對不可能參與此事
End of story.
不說了
See the look on their faces when we whipped out our badges?
你看到我們拿出軍徽時 他們臉上的表情了嗎
They looked like Ralph Terry
他們看起來像比爾馬澤羅斯基
when Bill Mazeroski hit his game seven walk-off homer on him.
在第七場比賽中 打出本壘打時的拉夫爾特里
Mazeroski? New rule, kid,
馬澤羅斯基 新規矩 孩子
you can't reference
你不能引用
shit from more than a decade before you were born.
你出生十多年前的人的例子
Go, Bucs.
滾開 海盜
We're so close to wrapping up this case I can taste it.
我們就快結案了
What do you think they're gonna give us-- Commendations, promotions?
你覺得他們會給我們什么  表揚 升職
I like the sound of that.
聽起來還不錯
Pump the brakes, Major.
就此打住 少校
There's still a hell of a lot of work ahead.
還有一大堆工作要做呢
More arrests to be made. Infrastructure to dismantle.
還要逮捕更多人 要拆除基礎設施
Whole networks of cargo planes, jeeps and helicopters across three continents.
調查跨越三大洲的 貨機 吉普車 直升機網絡
Just take the W, Gramps.
老爺爺 慶祝勝利吧
Don't sass your elders.
不要辱罵長輩
Yeah. Take it easy on him, guys. He hasn't had his nap yet.
就是 對他好點 他都不打瞌睡的
Damn. Looks like we got some Ivory Soap over here, Reacher.
好家伙 看來我們這里有象牙皂啊 雷徹
Meaning?
什么意思
Meaning this shit's so pure it floats.
意思是 這玩意很純 會漂起來
How pure?
有多純
Ninety-nine percent.
百分之九十九
No wonder kids are getting hooked on this shit left and right.
難怪到處都是迷上這玩意的孩子
At ease, sports fans, don't get up.
放松 體育迷們 不用站起來
I hear congratulations are in order.
我聽說就快結案了
That's quite the buy 'n bust.
臥底買賣收獲頗豐啊
Kilos of poison
幾公斤的毒品
and a handful of scumbag dealers off the streets
還有幾個被逮捕的毒販
and ratting on their friends for us.
向我們出賣他們的朋友
These are the small fish. We'll catch the sharks soon enough.
這些都是小魚 我們很快就會釣到大魚的
What did I tell you when you started this thing?
你開始查這事的時候 我怎么跟你說的
This case is gonna be a monster. Unleash the hounds.
“這個案子會是個怪物 所以關門放狗”
Seems you did.
看來你做到了
Speaking of monsters,
說到怪物
how's Hortense the Fourth?
霍滕斯四世怎么樣了
20 months, already into his terrible twos.
二十個月前 已經進入可怕的兩歲期了
Apparently, he's a prodigy.
顯然 他是個神童
Good work, everyone. Good work.
各位 干得好
Talking about a prodigy,
說起神童
you're about to hit your Bacardi milestone.
你就要達到百加得151里程碑了
151 cases closed.
已經偵破151起案件了
Don't add it to the stats sheets till it's done.
在案子完成前 不要加到統計表里
People in our profession re sent overseas
我們這一行的人會被派往海外
awhere we're shot at, bombed, blasted from IEDs.
在那里 我們會被槍擊 被轟炸 被簡易爆炸裝置炸飛
Then these assholes make more money selling
然后這些混蛋會靠賣這玩意
this shit than all our pensions combined.
賺的比我們所有人的養老金總和都多
It's fucked up.
真不公平
All I'm saying.
我就說說而已
How much is 48 bricks worth, anyway?
對了 48公斤值多少錢
one's missing. There's 47, not 48.
少了一公斤 是47公斤 不是48公斤
In an investigation, details matter.
在調查中 細節很重要
Brick of heroin's a hell of a detail.
海洛因的數量是個細節
That's impossible. I counted 48 at point of sale.
那不可能 我在銷售點數過 是48公斤
Either you miscounted or they palmed one back to short you.
要么是你數錯了 要么就是有人遞錯了
No, no, no. You do shit like that, you're not in the game for long.
不會 只有新手才會犯這種錯誤
I know we loaded 48 bricks into Swan's ride.
我知道我們 往斯旺的車里裝了48公斤
Let's check your car.
我們查查你的車
Nothing.
什么都沒有
Mystery solved.
謎團解開了
Must have fallen back there when I was driving and gotten stuck.
肯定是我開車的時候掉到后面卡住了
Guess the first round's on me tonight for that fuckup.
因為這個失誤 我猜今晚第一輪該我請客
Losing a key of H, I'd say that's worth two rounds.
掉了一公斤的海洛因 我得說應該請兩輪
What?
什么
Nothing.
沒什么
I'd actually forgotten about that, but it doesn't support your argument.
其實我都忘記這件事了 但這不支持你的論點
Swan could have been stealing drugs and just panicked and gave them back.
斯旺可能本來偷了毒品 而他只是驚慌失措 并將其歸還
Maybe he regretted letting a chance at big money go by.
也許他后悔錯過了這個賺大錢的機會
Maybe something like Little Wing came along
也許小翅膀項目來了
and he couldn't pass up that kind of opportunity again.
他不能再次錯過賺錢的機會
That's a lot of maybes. My gut tells me he's a good man.
有很多種可能 我的直覺告訴我他是個好人
Your gut's never been wrong before?
你的直覺以前從沒出過錯嗎
You know what I think?
你知道我是怎么想的嗎
You want Swan to be innocent because you hired him into the 110th,
你希望斯旺是無辜的 因為是你招募他到110小組的
and if he's involved in something like this,
如果他參與此事 你會做一些蠢事
you'd do something stupid like blame yourself for our friends' deaths.
比如你會因為我們朋友的死而自責
Which, like I said, would be stupid.
而正如我所說 這樣很蠢
Let's just see what O'Donnell found.
我們看看奧唐納發現了什么
- Mr. Mason? - Dr. Elzogby.
梅森先生 我是埃爾佐格比醫生
So, I read your intake, and upon first glance, I got to say,
我看了你的病歷 乍一看 我不得不說
got a few questions.
有幾個問題
Look, I like a payday as much as the next guy, but you're quite a handsome fella.
我和所有人一樣都喜歡錢 但你是個英俊的小伙子
Now, I'm not here to tell you how to live your life, but
我不會告訴你該怎么過你的生活
are you really certain you want me to give you a new face?
但你真的想讓我給你整個新面孔嗎
In a manner of speaking.
從某種意義上來說
Don't struggle.
別掙扎
You're a doctor, you know what's happening.
你是醫生 你知道發生了什么
Your trachea is severed.
你的氣管被割破了
Blood is entering your lungs, you're drowning,
血液正在肺部 你快憋死了
your brain is deprived of oxygen and your nervous system's shutting down.
你的大腦缺氧 神經系統停止工作
So, by now, you can barely see me
所以現在你幾乎看不到我
and now you can't hear me and now...
現在你還聽不到我說話 而現在
...you're dead.
你死了
I'm just gonna go and have a word with your secretary.
我要和你的秘書說句話
Daniel Boyd, Senator Lavoy's legislative director.
丹尼爾博伊德 拉沃伊參議員的立法主任
Spoiled dipshit who's never lifted anything heavier
被寵壞的蠢貨 一輩子從沒舉起過
than a Grey Goose bottle in his life.
任何比灰雁酒瓶更重的東西
C-plus student who got into UVA and Georgetown Law
以C+的成績進入弗吉尼亞大學
thanks to Mommy and Daddy's connections. Real party boy.
和喬治敦法學院 這都多虧了他父母的關系
Two dismissed DWIs in college.
真正的派對男孩
Second year of law school, gets caught with a sex worker.
法學院第二年 他被抓到嫖娼
Charges mysteriously disappeared.
指控神秘消失
Took his 2.3 GPA straight into private practice.
平均成績2.3 直接進入私人律所
And now he drafts legislation that decides the fate of the free world,
而現在他負責起草 決定我們命運的法案
telling his boss to vote on whatever benefits the lobbyists who wooed him best.
讓他的老板給符合最會討好他的 游說者的利益的內容投票
So, he was born somewhere between third and home base
所以他含著金鑰匙出生
and never heard the word "consequence."
從沒聽說過“后果”這個詞
You gonna pull a few moves from your sleazy-adjacent playbook?
你要用你那招 “比不道德差一點”的伎倆嗎
That's the general idea.
我就是這么想的
Boyd's gonna be in Boston tonight for a fundraiser event at the Pops.
博伊德今晚將在波士頓 參加通俗樂團的籌款活動
We'll set him up like a bowling pin.
我們可以設個局 輕易拿捏他
Yeah. You pick up the phone.
- 怎么  - 你竟然接電話了
I thought maybe you couldn't answer because you broke your hand
我還以為你開車闖進那棟辦公樓時
when you drove the fucking car through the office building.
弄傷了手 所以沒法接呢
I didn't get hurt at all.
我根本沒受傷
You think this is funny?
你覺得這很有趣嗎
I told you no more cowboy shit.
我跟你說了 “別再搞牛仔那套”
The car belonged to one of their employees.
那輛車屬于他們的一名員工
I was returning it.
我是去還車的
Listen, wiseass,
聽我說 大聰明
my boss almost punched my ticket because of you.
我的老大因為你們差點把我開除了
Well, maybe that's a good thing
也許那是件好事
'cause members of my unit are falling from the sky like raindrops and you haven't done shit.
因為我小隊的成員瀕臨死亡 而你什么都沒做
Hey, hey. I want everything you got on New Age.
嘿 我想知道 你們從新時代得到的所有線索
- You understand? - Fine.
- 明白嗎  - 好的
That's why I answered the phone this time. I actually have a reason to talk to you.
這就是我這次接電話的原因 我有理由跟你說話了
I'm gonna send you their security team roster.
我會把他們的安保團隊名單發給你
Run background checks, see what connections these guys have.
查一下這些人有什么聯系
W... Wait, wait, wait. What do you think-- I'm here to do your clerical work?
等等 怎么 你覺得 我是來給你們做文書工作的
Yup.
是啊
We're busy heading off to Boston.
我們正忙著去波士頓
What's in Boston?
波士頓有什么
The symphony.
交響樂
Goddamn it.
他媽的
Before we head north, though, Dixon and I should go talk to Marlo Burns,
但在我們去北邊之前 迪克森和我應該去跟馬洛伯恩斯談談
step on her neck a little bit.
給她施點壓
Address is online.
網上有地址
Right there is why I don't have a house. Yeah, that's the reason.
- 這就是為何我不買房子 - 是啊 好借口
So, while we do all the work, what are you guys gonna do?
那么 我們干活的時候 你們要做什么
Oh, we're gonna go score some drugs.
我們要去拿些毒品
Howdy.
你們好啊
Oh, shit. Five-O! Five-O!
- 見鬼  - 警察
Well, that's just rude.
真沒禮貌
This just ain't your week.
你這周運氣不好
Find a new line of work, asshole.
混蛋 找份新工作吧
She's got a kid.
她有個孩子
House clear.
室內安全
Affirmative.
已確認
Anything interesting?
有什么有趣的發現嗎
I mean, just some expensive jewelry Marlo left behind.
只有馬洛留下的一些昂貴的珠寶
Left behind?
留下的
Think she bugged out?
你覺得她跑了
She exited out the back door without locking it,
她從后門出去了 門都沒鎖
clothes are all over, clearly packed in a hurry.
衣服扔得到處都是 顯然是匆忙打包的
Closet and... cabinets are open.
衣櫥和櫥柜是開著的
Well, she took her toothbrush and toothpaste.
她拿走了牙刷和牙膏
Kidnappers don't care about oral hygiene.
綁匪通常不關心口腔衛生
Jane's a gamer.
簡是個玩家
Got good taste.
品味不錯
Uh, you might want to come and see this.
你可能想來看看這個
Who the hell goes on the lam and leaves their cash stash behind?
誰會逃跑的時候 不帶上儲備的現金啊
Apparently, Marlo Burns.
顯然 馬洛伯恩斯不會
So, to confirm, you've reserved a Cadillac Escalade,
確認一下 您預訂了一輛凱迪拉克凱雷德
to be returned within three days' time to JFK Airport.
三天后返還到肯尼迪機場 對嗎
That's correct.
沒錯
And to thank you for your loyalty,
為了答謝老顧客
we've upgraded you to a SiriusXM Platinum listening experience, free of charge.
我們免費給您升級到 SiriusXM白金聆聽體驗
Wonderful.
太棒了
Thank you for your business, Dr. Elzogby. Have a wonderful drive.
謝謝惠顧 埃爾佐格比醫生 祝您旅途愉快
Would you like this?
你想要這個嗎
Do you know why I love comic books so much?
你知道我為什么這么喜歡漫畫書嗎
Well, look at you.
看看你
Don't you feel more civilized now, Ms. Doolittle?
你不覺得現在更文明了嗎 杜立特女士
Wait, where are the clothes you were wearing? Garbage.
- 你之前穿的那身衣服在哪里  - 垃圾桶
Garbage, why?
垃圾桶 為什么
I'm already carrying boots.
我已經提著靴子了
If I had any more clothes, pretty soon I'd need a suitcase.
如果我還有更多衣服的話 很快我就需要手提箱了
I got a suitcase, I need a house to keep it in.
要是我有了手提箱 我需要一個房子來存放它
Then I need a car for the driveway.
然后我還需要一輛車停在車道上
Before you know it, I'm filling out all kinds of forms.
很快 我就得填寫各種表格
So, a spare shirt's just too much of an attachment for you?
所以 對你來說 一件備用襯衫太累贅了
Anyone ever diagnose you as a sociopath?
有人診斷說你是反社會人格嗎
Diagnosed? No.
診斷 沒有
So... what do you make of Marlo Burns taking off
那么 你覺得馬洛伯恩斯 為什么慌忙逃跑
with just some clothes and leaving all that cash behind?
只帶了幾件衣服 把所有現金都留下
Not sure yet.
我還不確定
Well, she did take her toothbrush.
她確實拿走了牙刷
She could be your soul mate.
她應該是你的靈魂伴侶吧
Shut up.
閉嘴
Not one word.
一個字都別說
Holy shit. That's two words.
- 天啊 - 那是兩個字了
Another one, and I'll shove this kitten heel right up your ass.
再說一個字 我就把這個小高跟插進你屁眼里
I'm just saying you look nice. You both look nice.
我只是說你很漂亮 你們倆都看起來不錯
We look like the assholes on top of a wedding cake.
我們看起來就像婚禮蛋糕上的混蛋
Here, I'll pay you back in a month when my pension lands.
給 等我的養老金到賬 我會在一個月內還給你的
Yeah, your pension won't cover that suit.
你的養老金可買不起那套西服
Or the hotel room. Or the plane ticket.
也付不起酒店房間 機票也付不起
I'll pay you back in two months.
我會在兩個月內還清
Okay.
好的
Everyone ready?
大家都準備好了嗎
Let's go listen to some boring-ass music.
我們去聽無聊的音樂吧
Okay.
好的
And, uh, close your mouth, boss. You're catching flies.
閉上嘴巴 老大 你的嘴巴大得都快進蒼蠅了
Excuse me.
借過
Thank you. Pardon me.
謝謝 對不起
- Excuse me. - Of course. Okay.
- 借過 - 沒事
Oh, no, it's...
不對 這...
Apologies. Not at all.
- 抱歉 - 沒事
I'm-I'm sorry. I'm a little turned around. I don't know if I have
對不起 我有點暈頭轉向的 我不知道我的座位
orchestra seats or floor box seats,
是在樂隊席還是在樓層包廂
and I actually don't even know what that means.
我其實都不知道這是什么意思
- Okay, well... - Do you mind? Let's just see what we got here.
- 介意嗎  - 我們看看票上寫的什么
Hmm, the mezzanine, that's where you are, but... Okay.
- 夾層樓 那是你的位置... - 好的
that just simply won't cut it. You see, you want to be down here.
...但那座位可不怎么樣 你會想坐在這里
The sound, it just wraps around you like a fleece.
聲音就像羊毛一樣包圍著你
How about I swap your ticket with my aide when he arrives?
等我的助手來了 你跟他換個位置吧
Wouldn't he mind?
他不介意嗎
Well, not if he wants to keep his job.
他要是想保住工作 就不會介意
Please, take a seat.
請坐吧
Thank you.
謝謝
In the bag.
穩操勝券
We go 13/14s. 8/13s.
我們有13/14 8/13
Over seven months, six-day working weeks.
總共七個月 每周工作六天
Maybe a time sheet clocking hours? Maybe a ratings scale? I don't know.
也許是一個記錄時間的時間表  也許是一種評級標準 我不知道
Top you off?
需要加水嗎
Yeah. Yes, ma'am.
- 需要 - 需要 女士
And when you get the chance, could you bring me the bill? This guy doesn't have any money.
還有 請把賬單拿給我 好嗎  這家伙沒錢
Sure. Let me tally it up for you.
當然可以 讓我幫你統計一下
Great.
太棒了
It's a tally.
這是統計
What?
什么
Here.
這里
13/14ths.
13/14
Something happened 13 times when it was supposed to happen 14 times.
某件事發生了13次 但本來應該發生14次
Uh, here, 11 out of 13. Eight out of 11.
這里 11次的13次 8次的11次
Hey, bud, I just...
嘿 伙計 我只是...
Okay, what did I tell you?
好的 我怎么跟你說的
Hands are for helping, not hitting.
手是用來幫忙的 不是用來打人的
Apologize to your brother. Share your Legos, okay?
向你的兄弟道歉 把你的樂高給他玩 好嗎
I love you.
我愛你
To the moon and back.
我對你的愛可以往返月球
Okay, bye for now.
好的 再見了
Sorry, I don't know why I gave them my burner number, uh...
對不起 我不知道 我為什么要給他們我的一次性手機號
Well, you look happy.
你看起來很開心
I did the math.
我算了一下
There were 2,197 total events, whatever they were.
有2197個事件 不管具體是什么事
But they only succeeded 1,547 times. But that's not the interesting number.
但只成功了1547次 但這個數字并不有趣
Look how many times they didn't get the outcome they wanted.
看看他們有多少次 沒得到他們想要的結果
2,197 minus 1,547.
2197減去1547
Six hundred and fifty. Holy shit.
650天啊
Six fifty at 100K each.
六千五 每手十萬
It's all connected somehow.
這一切都以某種方式聯系在一起
So...
那么...
So... hands are for helping?
那么 “手是用來幫忙的”
You have brass knuckles in your pocket.
你口袋里還裝著銅指虎
I got a PAW Patrol Band-Aid and some playground sand, too.
我有《狗狗巡邏隊》的創可貼 還有操場的沙子
Look, they call nonstop when I'm not there.
聽著 我不在的時候 他們不停地打電話 我...
And when I am there, it's, you know,
我在家的時候
7:00 a.m. weekend soccer games,
要早上7點去周末足球比賽
teacher conferences,
參加教師會議
scheduled sex with the wife.
與妻子預訂的做愛
I am no longer my own man.
我不再孑然一身
And you wouldn't trade it for anything in the world.
你不會拿它換世界上任何東西
Not for $65 million.
六千五百萬美元都不行
You are a changed man, O'Donnell.
你徹底變了 奧唐納
Yep. Maybe you should give it a go, huh?
是啊 也許你應該試試
Buy some land, start a family.
買些土地 組建個家庭
You'd be the scariest guy at PTA, but you'd be a good dad.
你會是親師會上最可怕的人 但你會是個好爸爸
- If I had land, I'd get four or five... - Four or five dogs.
- 要是我有土地 我會有四... - 四五條狗
You'd get four or five dogs, no woman?
你會有四五條狗 沒有女人
Not even Dixon?
連迪克森都不要
She's a friend.
她是朋友
Okay.
好吧
Whatever you say. That was some dress, though.
隨你怎么說吧 就像是一件衣服
Hell of a dress.
是一件很好的衣服
From Neagley. It's intermission.
是內格利的消息 現在是中場休息
Dixon and Boyd are leaving now.
迪克森和博伊德現在要走了
There they are.
他們在那里
That's one hell of a dress.
真是一件很好的衣服啊
My car's around the corner. Does that work?
我的車在拐角處 那樣可以嗎
I'll follow anywhere you lead, gorgeous.
我會跟著你走 美女
- Well, let's go party. - Okay.
- 我們去派對吧 - 好的
Look at her.
看看她
Boyd didn't stand a chance.
博伊德沒機會
Neagley again. She says my guy's in place.
又是內格利 她說我的人就位了
Hey, this friend of yours. He's gonna come through for us, yeah?
嘿 你的這位朋友會幫我們 對吧
If he was in the Army, I'd have asked him to join the 110th.
如果他在軍隊的話 我會邀請他加入110小組
Come here.
過來
Oh, you're all riled up.
你都興奮了
Well, what can I say? Classical music gets my motor running.
我能說什么 古典音樂讓我興奮
Yeah, well, drop it to second, Speed Racer. Let's have a little primer first.
慢一點 極速賽車手 我們先來點前戲
You're not messing around. All right.
你不是在胡鬧 好吧
- There we go. Ooh. Ooh. - Yeah. Yes.
- 好啦 好的 拿著這個 - 是的
Okay, hold this. Hold... hold that.
拿著
I never know how thick or thin to make these things.
我一直不知道要弄多厚或者多薄...
Hey, allow me.
嘿 我來吧
Thank you.
謝謝
Okay. Ladies first?
好了 女士優先
Oh, no, you did the work, you get the reward.
不 你弄的 你應該得到獎勵
If you insist.
恭敬不如從命
Shit. Shit. Just-just play it cool, just play it cool. Just play it cool.
糟了 努力保持冷靜
Sir, you're gonna want to put the drugs away and step out of the car.
先生 你得把毒品收起來 然后下車
They're not my drugs.
那不是我的毒品
Which drugs--
哪些毒品
the ones on your mirror or up your nose?
你化妝鏡里的 還是你鼻子上的
You think I own a makeup mirror? They're all hers.
你覺得化妝鏡是我的嗎  全都是她的
Not what she's saying, and she wasn't holding it.
跟她說的不一樣 而且她又沒拿化妝鏡
And she already offered up blood and urine.
她已經提出進行血檢和尿檢
Do you want to offer up blood and urine?
你想進行血檢和尿檢嗎
Listen, Officer,
聽我說 長官
I hate putting it this way, but... do you know who I am?
我不愿意這么說 但你知道我是誰嗎
I do, actually, Mr. Boyd.
我其實知道 博伊德先生
And I know that woman in the car wasn't Mrs. Boyd.
我還知道車里的那個女人 不是博伊德太太
And I have a special distaste for people
我特別討厭那些
who don't appreciate the sanctity of marriage.
不珍惜神圣的婚姻的人
I also know you work for Senator Lavoy.
我也知道你是拉沃伊參議員的手下
But when I ran your name in the system,
但我在系統里查你的名字時
it set off bells and whistles at the local FBI office.
觸發了當地聯邦調查局的警報
They sent a couple of their boys down here just to talk to you.
他們派了幾個人過來跟你聊聊
And it seems they don't care who your boss is.
他們似乎并不在乎你的老板是誰
Special Agent Jack Margrave.
我是杰克馬格雷福特工
This is Special Agent Blake.
這是布雷克特工
Lieutenant Oscar Finlay.
我是奧斯卡芬雷中尉
Yeah, I'm not talking without my lawyer.
律師不在場 我不會說話
You want to lawyer up?
你想請律師嗎
Fine. Call them.
好的 給他打電話吧
I will. And they'll have me out of here within the hour.
我會的 他們一小時內 就會把我弄出去
You know...
你知道
...that's just gonna be too late.
那就太晚了
Because by the time they get here,
因為等他們到這里時
we'll already have the story of a senator's legislative director
我們就已經 在《環球報》和《先驅報》的頭版
in the wrong woman's car with a snout full of booger sugar
刊登了一位參議員的立法主任
on the front page of the Globe and the Herald.
坐在錯誤的女人的車里 鼻子里全是可卡因的報道
You see,
你知道
this is not college or law school, son.
這不是大學或法學院 孩子
You're not some spoiled rich kid barely rocking a C-plus.
你也不是被寵壞的 勉強拿到C+的富家子弟
You're a Beltway man now.
你現在是個政客
Kind of guy that people enjoy knocking down a peg or two.
是人們喜歡搞垮的那種人
So these charges,
所以這些指控
they're not just gonna get swept under the rug.
它們可不會逃過大眾的法眼
We're not gonna let 'em.
我們不會讓他們這樣
Want to know why?
想知道原因嗎
Okay. Why?
好吧 為什么
'Cause we don't like you.
因為我們不喜歡你
I don't even know why you're here.
我甚至都不知道你們為什么來這里
We're here 'cause we want to know everything there is to know
我們在這里是因為 我們想知道關于小翅膀計劃的
about Little Wing.
所有信息
- I should probably... - Yeah, you should.
- 我也許應該... - 你應該
Yeah. I'm gonna call Mr. Boyd's wife.
是啊 我要給 博伊德先生的妻子打電話
Eh, she's probably worried about him over in D.C.
她可能在華盛頓擔心他
Worried sick.
非常擔心
You know, happy wife, happy life, huh?
老婆開心 生活舒心
Okay. Fine.
好吧
- Hello? - Wrong number.
- 你好  - 我打錯了
Talk.
說話
It's not that big of a deal.
這沒什么大不了的
Little Wing is just a code name.
小翅膀只是個代號
For what?
什么的代號
For a new technology currently in development.
一項目前正在開發的新技術的代號
Some incredible anti-missile software
一個令人難以置信的反導彈軟件
originally developed to protect commercial aircraft,
它最初是為保護商用飛機而開發的
but a certain aeronautics company approached us.
但某個航空公司找到了我們
Let me guess--
讓我猜猜
New Age?
新時代
That's right. New Age.
是的 新時代
They found the software could be tweaked.
他們發現該軟件可以做些調整
It could be used in missiles and not just against them.
它可以用于導彈中 而且不僅僅是針對它們
It could be scaled down
它還可以縮小
and installed in portable shoulder-fired surface-to-air weaponry.
安裝在便攜式肩扛式地對空武器中
The software allows missiles to defeat
這個軟件能讓導彈擊破
all known countermeasures. How?
- 所有已知的對抗措施 - 怎么做到的
That's a question for a nerd in a lab coat, man.
那是穿著實驗室制服的 書呆子才會問的問題
Okay? All I know is
好吧 我只知道
that missiles shot from the ground completely bypass their target,
從地面發射的導彈 能完全繞過它們的目標
making pilots believe the threat has passed,
讓飛行員相信威脅已經過去
and then they recalibrate, turn around,
然后它們重新校準 轉身
zero back in on the aircraft and reattack.
重新瞄準飛機 重新進行攻擊
It's death from above and there is no way to avoid it.
這必死無疑 無法避免
You fire, you hit your target. Period.
你開火 就能射中目標 就是這樣
And what's Senator Lavoy's involvement?
那拉沃伊參議員參與了什么
Well, the project required an appropriation bill, all right?
項目需要一個撥款法案 好嗎
You want to get one passed?
你想要通過一個法案
You're looking at years of bureaucratic bullshit
就得面對多年的繁文縟節
all thanks to some arcane laws on modifying civilian tech.
這都要歸功于一些 關于修改民用技術的古怪法律
But Lavoy knew Little Wing would slingshot our military into the future,
但拉沃伊知道小翅膀 會帶領我們的軍隊走向未來
so if we just sat on our hands,
所以如果我們袖手旁觀
waiting for it to go through the proper channels,
等待申請通過正規渠道
it would never happen.
那永遠都無法落實
So I'm assuming Lavoy didn't clear up the red tape
所以我猜拉沃伊沒有以最體面的方式
in the most reputable manner?
清除繁文縟節
I helped bury the proposal in a thousand-page statute
我幫忙把提案塞進了 一份一千頁的法規中
while Lavoy shook hands and drummed up votes.
與此同時 拉沃伊負責握手拉選票
No one even knew it was in there.
甚至都沒人知道法案里有這個
And he did this out of the goodness of his heart?
他純粹是好心做這事
To protect democracy?
為了保護民主
No fat envelopes slipped inside newspapers on park benches?
沒有收紅包之類的
Grow the fuck up, okay?
成熟點 好嗎
It's D.C. It's how shit gets done.
這是華盛頓特區 這是辦事的規矩
Besides, Lavoy knew Little Wing would save lives.
此外 拉沃伊知道小翅膀會拯救生命
I mean...
我的意思是
everyone made fun of the Star Wars defense program,
每個人都嘲笑星球大戰的防御計劃
but, hey, look at where we are now.
但看看我們現在的處境
Everyone's trying to shoot projectiles out of the air.
每個人都想從空中發射炮彈
Little Wing can knock anything out of the sky.
小翅膀可以擊中空中的任何物體
Anything?
任何物體
Like commercial aircraft?
比如商用飛機
You fire, you hit the target.
你開火 就能擊中目標
You said so yourself. Yeah, but it's our tech. We have it.
- 你自己說的 - 對 但這是我們的技術 歸我們所有
Nobody else can get their hands on it.
其他人都無法得到它
Nothing like you're thinking is going to happen.
你們想的那種事是不會發生的
New Age is incredibly secure. Both of their facilities
新時代非常安全 他們的兩個場所都采用了
- implement state-of-the-art... - Both facilities?
- 最先進的... - 兩個場所
What do you mean?
什么意思
New Age has two bases.
新時代有兩個基地
Software made in New York,
軟件是在紐約開發的
hardware at a manufacturing plant in Denver.
硬件是在丹佛的制造工廠制造的
What else can you tell us?
還有什么
Nothing. That's all I know. I swear.
沒了 我發誓我就知道這些
Hey, Lavoy and me-- we-we cut some corners,
嘿 拉沃伊和我 我們走了捷徑
we did some stuff we should not have done,
我們確實做了一些不該做的事
but it was all to get a defense bill passed,
但這都是為了讓國防法案通過
protect the country.
保護國家
How'd that work out?
那結果如何
Hey, excuse me. So, are the drug charges getting dropped or what?
嘿 抱歉 所以毒品指控會被撤銷嗎
I don't know. I'm not a cop.
我不知道 我不是警察
Heck of a surprise getting a call from you.
真意外 居然接到你的電話
Hell of a surprise hearing you're wearing the badge again.
聽說你又戴上警徽了 真是太意外了
Lieutenant, no less.
中尉 彼此彼此
Yeah, well, retirement didn't suit me.
是啊 退休可不適合我
Speaking of suits, see you're still sporting the tweed.
說起來 我看你還穿著呢子大衣
Reliable as ever, Finlay.
一如既往的可靠 芬雷
Speak for yourself.
你是說你自己吧
What was it you told me when we first met--
我們初次見面時 你跟我說了什么
trouble always seems to find you?
“麻煩似乎總是找上你”
You kill a whole lot of people?
你殺了很多人嗎
Here and there. You need my help?
- 時不時 - 需要幫忙嗎
Already gave it.
你已經幫我了
You still spinning that wedding ring?
你還在轉那枚結婚戒指嗎
Here and there. But feeling better every day.
時不時 但感覺一天比一天好
- And the dog? - Jack eats too much.
- 狗呢  - 杰克很能吃
Just like his namesake.
狗如其名
Today, boss. Car's running, and if I don't get out of this straitjacket soon,
今天 老大 汽車正在行駛 如果我不盡快脫掉這件緊身衣
things are gonna get ugly. Neagley?
- 事情會變得很難看的 - 內格利
Didn't recognize you. Looking good.
我都沒認出你 看起來很美
Mind your business, elbow patches.
別多管閑事 補丁男
Hey, you heard the lady.
你聽到這位女士說的了
If I don't have her in jeans in 20 minutes,
如果我20分鐘內不讓她穿上牛仔褲
I'm done for.
我就完蛋了
See you around, Reacher.
回見 雷徹
See you around, Finlay.
回見 芬雷
So, Little Wing could be our next 9/11.
所以小翅膀可能會鑄就下一起911
What are our directives?
我們的指令是什么
You and Dixon go to Denver.
你和迪克森去丹佛
The Little Wing software is useless without the missile hardware,
小翅膀軟件需要導彈硬件
and that's where it's made.
那是硬件的制造地
Maybe you can gum up the works, keep the missiles out of the wrong hands.
也許你們可以干擾一下 以免導彈落入壞人之手
O'Donnell and I will head down to D.C.
奧唐納和我會去華盛頓特區
Want to swing by Homeland, see what they know about A.M.
我想去國土安全局 看看他們是否知道AM的事
If taking out airplanes is his M.O., they might have some intel on him.
如果他的作案手法是將人扔出飛機 他們可能有些情報
How do you figure we're gonna do that?
我們要怎么做
You think we're just gonna knock on the door and say, "Can the DoD come out and play?"
你覺得我們就直接敲門說 “國防部能出來玩嗎 ”
My brother worked for Homeland.
我兄弟在國土安全局工作
His contacts can help us.
他的聯系人能幫到我們
Oh, no shit. How's Joe doing these days?
對哦 喬最近過得怎么樣
He's dead.
他死了
I'm starving. We should eat.
我餓了 我們應該吃飯
Dibs on the bathroom. I need to get changed.
我有權用浴室 我得換衣服
Yeah? You gonna throw it in the garbage like our sociopathic friend here?
是嗎 你要把這衣服扔進垃圾桶 就像這位反社會朋友一樣嗎
Oh, why, you want to borrow it?
不會 怎么 你想借
Oh, yeah. I got the ass for it.
是啊 我很喜歡
Hate to ruin prom night,
我很討厭破壞舞會之夜
but hand over your guns.
但交出你們的槍
What makes you think we have guns?
你為什么覺得我們有槍
We were told you'd be packing, Reacher.
有人跟我們說你們有槍 雷徹
They also tell you you'd die tonight?
他們還跟你說 今晚你會死嗎
I'll die? That's funny.
我會死 真搞笑
No guns, so no noise.
沒有槍 所以沒有噪音
They said you were smart.
他們說你們很聰明
I'm gonna cut you,
我要砍死你
gut you
割了你
and leave you...
讓你...
Everyone okay?
大家都還好嗎
Yeah. It'll heal.
還好 會愈合的
Never better.
不能更好了
Fucked up my shoes,
我的鞋壞了
but I'm fine.
但我沒事
Yeah.
嗯
Before you ask if it's done, it is,
不用你問出口 已經完事了
just not in the way you hoped for.
只是跟你希望的方式不同
You're causing a very complex operation a lot of problems.
你造成了很多復雜的問題
Sixty-five million dollars worth, Langston?
價值六千五百萬美元 蘭斯頓
Assume that's who I'm talking to.
我猜你就是蘭斯頓吧
Head of security?
安保部老大
Head of this whole thing?
整件事的老大
Maybe we've been approaching this the wrong way, Mr. Reacher.
也許我們一直在用 錯誤的方式處理此事 雷徹先生
Just Reacher.
叫我雷徹
Okay, Reacher. Why don't we make a deal?
好吧 雷徹 不如我們做筆交易吧
I have the means to give you anything you could ask for.
你想要什么我都能給你
What is it that you want?
你想要什么
I want to throw you out of a helicopter.
我想把你扔出直升機